<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- $Id: changelog.xml 2341 2011-08-01 23:05:30Z stian $ -->
<!-- @TODO make changelog.dtd -->
<!--DOCTYPE changelog SYSTEM "http://ninjaforge.com/dtd/changelog.dtd"-->

<changelogs>
    <version>1.1.4</version>
    <date>August 2nd 2011</date>
    <state>Maintenance Release
        <upgrade>Synced with the latest translation updates from our Transifex project.</upgrade>
        <upgrade>Clicking on links to posts in the topic you're viewing no longer reloads the page on HTML5 history api enabled browsers.</upgrade>
        <upgrade>Forum and topic views now include canonical metadata in the html head to prevent/fix duplicate content listings in search engines.</upgrade>
        <bugfix>Form labels no longer overlap the input element when the text overflows. This were particularly affecting the Settings layout in some translations.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Fixed issue where the Ninja Framework plugin autoloaded the Nooku Framework plugin so a fatal error were thrown.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Attachments did not follow usergroup permissions or attachment enable settings.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Fixed issue in Quickpanel logout URL that would cause PHP Notices, and empty LIMITS to be introduced on return URLs.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Forum icons only supported png files.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Performance bottleneck in Agora converter caused by a subquery is replaced by a much faster left join.</bugfix>
        <log>UI for toggling locked state on forums are longer available. Will be added back in 1.2 when the feature is fully implemented.</log>
    </state>

    <version>1.1.3</version>
    <date>July 27th 2011</date>
    <state>Security Release
        <security>Security audit performed on all SQL queries executed in Ninjaboard that doesn't use the automatic quoting in Nooku Framework for performance reasons to make sure they're not exploitable in any way.</security>
        <security>Hardened security in person controller in a SQL query that prevents duplicate screen names.</security>
        <security>Hardened security in 3 SQL queries used for searching in the posts, people and messages models.</security>
        <upgrade>Synced with the latest translation updates from our Transifex project.</upgrade>
    </state>

    <version>1.1.2</version>
    <date>July 22nd 2011</date>
    <state>Maintenance Release
        <upgrade>Synced with the latest translation updates from our Transifex project.</upgrade>
        <upgrade>Added options to allow the user to configure what links to show or not in Ninjaboard Quickpanel module.</upgrade>
        <bugfix>Fixed issue were there were no background on selected PM messages unless the browser were WebKit or Gecko based.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>SMF converter didn't correct whitepsace entities to the raw symbol.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Fixed issue with SMF converter were it would fail if the SMF installation did not have SEF urls turned on.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>"No topics yet" hint was displayed to super admins.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Fixed issue were moving a topic would change its status to unread.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Fixed issue were vertical scrollbars appeared in browsers like Safari on specific Joomla templates.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Resolved RTL CSS issues frontend in general on list views and in the backend toolbar.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Regression caused a too narrow width on lastpost columns on forum view, as well as a misaligned separator.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Regression caused overflowing topic subjects to no longer show an ellipsis in forum view.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Previewing a private message now works again.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Subscribe button would sometimes overlap the pagination in Forum view.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Fixed issue where buttons on the Person view didn't line up.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Fixed CSS issue where the reply button on the PM page got pushed down in non-WebKit browsers.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>The unread indicators on private messages had the wrong url to the unread.png icon.</bugfix>
    </state>

    <version>1.1.1</version>
    <date>July 15th 2011</date>
    <state>Maintenance Release
        <upgrade>UTF8 slugs no longer rely on iconv to transliterate properly.</upgrade>
        <upgrade>Synced with the latest translation updates from our Transifex project.</upgrade>
        <bugfix>Private Messaging javascript were incompatible with MooTools 1.2.5</bugfix>
        <bugfix>SEF router generated broken URLs for topics with 100 character long subjects.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Added a few missing strings in the translation master file.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Fatal Error: Call to undefined method ComNinjaHelperDefault::css() when site is in RTL mode on PHP 5.2.5</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Posts style wrapping sometimes didn't apply.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Major performance bottleneck fixed in read topics feature and in general forums and topics queries.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>404 headers were set when clicking Reply Topic button.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Performance bottleneck fixed in SEF router.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Some CSS3 gradients only worked in WebKit. Updated the css to support Opera 11+, FF 4+, IE10+ in addition to WebKit flavors.</bugfix>
    </state>

	<version>1.1</version>
	<date>July 8th 2011</date>
	<state>Major Release
		<!-- Changelog for 1.1 is very incomplete -->
		<new>Private Messaging, using a conversation based UI instead of an inbox/outbox.</new>
		<new>Vanity SEF urls for forums and topics.</new>
		<new>SMF converter added</new>
		<new>New "Ninjaboard Quickpanel" module, bundled with the core package.</new>
		<upgrade>Posts blocks now have same styling as forums blocks on the forums page. You can toggle the behavior from the Settings page.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Updated French translation - thanks lavsteph!</upgrade>
		<upgrade>SEF router upgraded with a cache layer for parsing and rendering, performance measured between 30%-50% on pages with a lot of links, due to the reduced amount of SQL queries and other expensive code.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>bbCode parser upgraded with a cache layer, performance increase measured between 10%-20% on pages with posts and signatures.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>URL slugs now transliterate UTF8 characters, even Greek!</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Added option to configure the lightbox rel attribute for image attachments.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Avatars now send proper caching headers to enable browser caching.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>ccBoard converter now supports html.</upgrade>
		<bugfix>Latest Posts on the user profile page displayed latest topics that were started by the user. It now shows the latest topics the user have contributed to not just started.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>.wrap no longer have float:left, this solves issues in for posts blocks in some templates not expanding the background to the full height of the post.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>The .poster-is-topic-creator class was only applied correctly if the last post were made by the topic starter.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Users were still able to configure email notification settings when email notifications were globally disabled.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed issue where search results didn't match by subject unless it was the first post in a topic.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed issues with plugins like Remember Me, where an additional page refresh were needed in order to be logged in to the forums.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed issue in bbCode parser where urls with closing tags with no whitespace or linebreaks first would lead to broken syntax.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed bug where a topic where still accessible by link if the parent forum allowed forum access, but had topics set to no access.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>SEF links in 3rd party extensions linking to forums that the user can't access were missing the alias, only showing the id due to ACL query WHERE statements.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed rare bug that caused forums to be accessible by link even when the ACL were configured to disallow it.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Duplicate/Redundant CSS fixed for the forum and topic icons in the list view.</bugfix>
		<log>All translations are now fully automated by Transifex, find us here: https://www.transifex.net/projects/p/ninjaboard/</log>
		<log>Maximum subject character length for posts have been changed from 255 to 100 in the database schema.</log>
	</state>

    <version>1.0.13</version>
    <date>June 16th 2011</date>
    <state>Maintenance Release
        <log>The #__ninjaboard_log_topic_reads table was missing from the uninstall.sql.</log>
        <log>Updated MySQL version checker to specify that it's the server version not client version being checked.</log>
    </state>

    <version>1.0.12</version>
    <date>May 24th 2011</date>
    <state>Maintenance Release
        <upgrade>Changed unread indicator on forums and topics to be a span tag instead of just a background image on the li tag itself.</upgrade>
        <bugfix>Fixed regression bug that caused the "Notify me when a reply is posted" checkbox when posting to no longer function.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Fixed issue where forums are marked as read when latest topic is viewed, disregarding other unread topics within a forum.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Fixed regression bug where an sql error would happen instead of a 404 when topic isn't found.</bugfix>
    </state>

    <version>1.0.11</version>
    <date>May 23th 2011</date>
    <state>Maintenance Release
        <new>Unread/read topics and forums now got indicators to show states, that can be customized by css.</new>
        <bugfix>Fixed bug where multiple tags would occur when line breaks were used in [code] and [quote] calls. Patched by Hook.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Built in updates failed to recognize 1.0.10 to be a more recent version than &lt;= 1.0.9.</bugfix>
    </state>

    <version>1.0.10</version>
    <date>May 19th 2011</date>
    <state>Maintenance Release
        <upgrade>Dutch translation files updated - thanks John Bartels!</upgrade>
        <bugfix>Fixed issue where adding an attachment file input in a post without selecting a file would show a "Filetype not supported" error.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Incompatibility with Warp6, patched by YOOtheme.</bugfix>
    </state>

    <version>1.0.9</version>
    <date>April 27th 2011</date>
    <state>Maintenance Release
        <upgrade>Performance optimization makes topic pages load twice as fast.</upgrade>
        <upgrade>Instead of automatically importing sample content when Ninjaboard got no data, you now see a notice in the administrator giving you the option to do it until you have at least 1 forum setup.</upgrade>
        <bugfix>Fixed annoying double encode issue with URLs that made special characters display in their entity form.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Fixed issue where scrollbars would appear in pre blocks and on long URLs in posts.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Fixed issue where New Topic and Reply Topic were shown when the user weren't authorized to perform those actions. Clicking them would result in blank pages with no error message, this is also fixed now.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Fixed CSS problems when previewing a post.</bugfix>
    </state>

    <version>1.0.8</version>
    <date>April 14th 2011</date>
    <state>Maintenance Release
        <upgrade>Swedish translation files updated - thanks Kristian Dahlén!</upgrade>
        <bugfix>Default Nooku Framework ACL caused users in the "Registered" group to be unable to post in the forums.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Regression in usergroup maps caused saving to fail, and also showed incorrect mapping for the "Unregistered" usergroup.</bugfix>
        <bugfix>Regression bug caused the sample content to no longer automatically import on first launch on new installs.</bugfix>
    </state>

	<version>1.0.7</version>
	<date>April 12th 2011</date>
	<state>Maintenance Release
	    <security>Vulnerability that allowed hidden posts to be displayed outside of ones ACL permissions patched.</security>
	    <new>New "View Profile" menu item type added, takes the users to their own profiles, or a login form if not logged in.</new>
		<new>Portuguese (Portugal) translation - thanks Cândido Pereira!</new>
		<upgrade>Converters now report how long a conversion took.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>/component/ninjaboard like SEF urls are now redirected to the right menu item linking to Ninjaboard to eliminate duplicate urls.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Nooku Framework snapshot upgraded to Alpha 2.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Ninjaboard adminstration tools can only be run by super administrators from now on.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Profile edit form updated to look much nicer in darker templates.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Fixed issue where avatar uploads might not work.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Usability for Profile Edit form improved regarding custom display name.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Spanish translation files updated - thanks Manuel Fazio!</upgrade>
		<upgrade>jQuery upgraded to 1.5.1.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Forums order option when creating menu items is now gone. Forums will now be sorted after your custom ordering at all times.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Email notification buttons now have a fixed width.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>All PNGs are crunched, faster loading and smaller installer packages.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>No longer fails silently when com_ninja or nooku framework is missing, you'll now get proper error messages.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Swedish translation files updated - thanks Kristian Dahlén!</upgrade>
		<bugfix>Tooltips related to Chameleon Settings were missing.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Form radio inputs were misaligned on Linux Firefox.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>PHP 5.3 users without date.timezone defined in their php.ini would get PHP warnings in areas Ninjaboard displayed dates.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Avatars didn't show in the backend when the default menu item wasn't a Ninjaboard type.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Link detector is now smart enough to check when it needs to add protocols to URLs.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Custom icon path mixed forward and back slashes</bugfix>
		<bugfix>SEF urls now show the alias for restricted forums instead of just the id.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Regression could cause redirects on post cancels to fail when SEF is turned on.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Regression caused topics to sort by first post instead of last post.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Regression caused email notifications to no longer work.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>If attachments were deleted on the filesystem, JFile warnings about not being able to open files would be thrown.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>JPEG attachments weren't recognized as images.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Regression in 1.0.6 caused a maximum of 20 items to show in many lists, like forum permissions, forum parent, usergroups in usergroups mapper and such.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Built in updates now works again.</bugfix>
	</state>

	<version>1.0.6</version>
	<date>February 27th 2011</date>
	<state>Maintenance Release
		<bugfix>Fixed issue where an SQL error occured if a user did not have permission to post.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Resolved JS error when adding a new Usergroup.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed a problem with the list limit not being set, sometimes causing timeouts.</bugfix>
	</state>

	<version>1.0.5</version>
	<date>February 20th 2011</date>
	<state>Maintenance Release
		<bugfix>Fixed error were Avatar quality slider in non-webkit browsers would always show as 0.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixing issue that caused some templates to mistakenly hide sidebars thinking the main layouts where form layouts.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Major performance bottleneck causing timeouts on larger forums when replying or editing a topic is now solved - thanks Nicholas Dionysopoulos!</bugfix>
	</state>

	<version>1.0.4</version>
	<date>February 19th 2011</date>
	<state>Maintenance Release
		<security>Vulnerability in the post preview function.</security>
		<new>Posts have now a few new dynamic css classes to them. They change depending on wether the poster is the topic creator, the poster rank, usergroups and more.</new>
		<new>Turkey translation - thanks Yagiz Ergenc!</new>
		<upgrade>German translation updated - thanks Wolfgang Naber!</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Agora converter learned to handle subscriptions.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Post editor now fades out toolbar buttons when in preview mode to make it more distinct from edit mode.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Now possible to globally disable email notifications.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Added option that lets you display the new topic button on a topic.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Session is now kept alive while composing posts.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Avatar uploads and management lacked on the backend compared to frontend.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>No longer needed to visit the dashboard to complete installations.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Norwegian translation updated.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>English translation files updated with new strings.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Post edit button now got a 'edit' class to make it easier to style.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Italian translation upgraded - thanks Valter Mura!</upgrade>
		<bugfix>Usergroups mapper works with IE8 once again, an unclosed div caused it to break.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed IE8 issue where post preview would cause text to overlap, making it unreadable.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Trailing whitespace in user search box were not trimmed.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed issue where searching in the Ninjaboard Users backend would reveal people that are disabled that would otherwise be hidden.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Signatures with images in them could cause text overlaps with the post text making it unreadable.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Sometimes a post could overlap and cause parts of the previous post to be unselectable (for instance you couldn't click a link).</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed issue where Watches filter would cause an http 500 error screen with an sql syntax error.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed missing Map icon on the Usergroups screen.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Ninjaboard no longer changes the scripts load order on site as it caused js errors on some sites. It's also more failsafe should multiple jQuery instances load on the same page.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Added compatability with Safety Extender - thanks zone.ee!</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Forum titles weren't vertically centered like topic titles when no forum descriptions.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Resolved styling issues with RocketTheme Grunge.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Compatibility fixes with the new 2011 RocketTheme templates.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Kunena converter failed on topic shadows (moved topics) due to typo.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Performance issues in Kunena converter.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixing issues with avatars on some host setups.</bugfix>
		<log>Removed post preview button as it mislead users into thinking it would preview the post on page, not just the editor text. We'll add back the preview button when it actually behaves like that.</log>
	</state>

	<version>1.0.3</version>
	<date>January 21th 2011</date>
	<state>Bugfix Release
		<bugfix>Regression in attachments and avatars.</bugfix>
	</state>

	<version>1.0.2</version>
	<date>January 20th 2011</date>
	<state>Bugfix Release
		<bugfix>Fixing regression introduced in 1.0.1 that resulted in various SQL syntax errors.</bugfix>
	</state>

	<version>1.0.1</version>
	<date>January 20th 2011</date>
	<state>Security Release
		<security>Security vulnerability in Nooku Framework exposed the database prefix on the site if user generated content had text like `#__menus`.</security>
	</state>

	<version>1.0</version>
	<date>January 15th 2011</date>
	<state>First Stable Release
		<new>Quick Reply</new>
		<new>Spanish translation - thanks Jon Neubauer!</new>
		<new>Portuguese (Brazil) translation - thanks Eni Rodrigues!</new>
		<upgrade>jQuery loading now respects the JFactory::getApplication()->get('jquery') convention.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Replaced the default (scary mask) avatar with a custom designed one.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Ability to add custom icons by using the Joomla! Media Manager. Use folders like /images/com_ninjaboard/forums, /images/com_ninjaboard/rank and /images/com_ninjaboard/topic.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Upgraded MooTools from 1.2.4 to 1.2.5 to resolve IE9 and IE8 problems.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Ability to set visibility on Usergroups, applied on the frontend.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Settings now automatically makes sure that at least one profile is set as default.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Improved post layout.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Added accesskey attributes to New Topic (key=N) and Reply Topic (key=R) buttons.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Topic urls now also include the subject as slug, not just the id.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Forum icon now shows on the regular forum layout, not just lists.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Option to show peoples usergroups in their posts and profiles.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Resolved performance bottlenecks in views due to canned code that were left behind.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Forum reordering no longer have the cases where you have to click multiple times to change the position in the list.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Image attachments markup updated with a rel="lightbox[postid]" to support lightbox plugins.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Post editor text now set to inherit the color in order to stay readable on dark templates without general forms styling.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Reply Topic and Create Topic buttons now always show, clicking it while logged out will render a login form, and redirect you to the post form once logged in.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Newest posts now in a list at the bottom while replying a topic.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Dedicated Preview button added when writing posts (as the magnifying glass in the editor weren't obvious).</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Compatibility added for the following admin templates: AdminPraise2, APLite, AdminPad, Stainless, AdminPraise3, JB Crisp, JB Simpla and RT MissionControl.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Attachments ease of use improved. Shows allowed file extensions, max upload filesize and more.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Dutch translation files updated - thanks John Bartels!</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Swedish translation files updated - thanks Kristian Dahlén!</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Filters (All | Enabled - Disabled) added to forums, settings and ranks in the administrator.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Norwegian translation files updated - thanks Svein Wisnaes and Torkil Johnsen!</upgrade>
		<bugfix>Various IE issues resolved.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Forum icons could not have whitespace in their filenames.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Labels did not inherit colors from the template, resulting in hard to read form labels in darker templates.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Breadcrumbs missed the "Forums" part in some cases.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>A new forum defaulted to the top of the list.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Forum headers didn't show anywhere.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Attachment permissions only applied on who could upload them. But not on who could see and download them.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Subforums missing from "Forum" view.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Blocked users showed in the Users list.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed breaking code due to changes in j!1.6 RC.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Any HTML were stripped out of posts.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>File attachment links broke when SEF urls with file endings were on.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Theme name missing from Settings view.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Disabled Ranks no longer render.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Ranks no longer render if a user don't have one, avoiding 404 image requests.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Topics and Posts in disabled forums could still be accessed by search, latest topics lists and on profile pages.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixing $params not defined notice in forums view when forums without subforums rendered.</bugfix>
	</state>

	<version>1.0RC7</version>
	<date>December 21st 2010</date>
	<state>Bugfix Release
		<new>Suhosin is now automatically detected, and instructions on how to configure it to allow Ninjaboard to run is provided.</new>
		<new>Option to disable avatars</new>
		<upgrade>Italian translation upgraded, and also includes the administrator - thanks Valter Mura!</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Forums view now renders forums that are without subforums.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Forum descriptions now support bbCode.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Sortables added to Usergroups allowing you to change the order of them.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>There's an ID column added to the users view.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Administrator Forums view now have a search field.</upgrade>
		<bugfix>Error when posting if there were no email notifications recipients.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Topics order is now sorting by the date of the last post instead of the first one, so active topics will be on top of the list.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Post editor didn't prepend [*] when creating lists, confusing users.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed issue where the Ninja system plugin would throw an Fatal error if com_ninja were uninstalled before Nooku Framework.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed rare case in SEF router that resulted in 404 messages when other variables were appended to a view=forum url.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixes done in Usergroup tables to make the AEC Ninjaboard Micro Integration work again.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Regression fixed with menu items Settings and Forums select popups.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Posts had an ordering issue.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Email notification links had faulty links when SEF is on.</bugfix>
	</state>

	<version>1.0.0RC6</version>
	<date>December 13th 2010</date>
	<state>Major Release
		<security>Low priority frontend XSS with image attachment file names.</security>
		<security>Low priority frontend XSS with post titles, only when editing one.</security>
		<security>Low priority admin XSS with search field not escaping output.</security>
		<security>Low priority admin XSS vulnerability where managers+ could exploit the forum title field.</security>
		<new>Chameleon now configurable under Settings. Page Class Suffixes are entirely optional as a result.</new>
		<new>Theme API enabled. Each theme may have its own settings that are shown conditionally under "Settings".</new>
		<new>Possible to select topic layout, wether to have pagination both top or bottom, or just at the bottom.</new>
		<new>Chameleon now also integrates with the pagination styling that your template provides.</new>
		<new>Users can define their own custom screen name, or to show username, or real name.</new>
		<new>Agora converter, supports avatars and attachments.</new>
		<new>Move topics added.</new>
		<new>ccBoard converter, support avatars and attachments.</new>
		<new>Italian frontend translation - thanks Valter Mura!</new>
		<new>Installable on Joomla! 1.6!</new>
		<new>New and improved installer that's much faster due to making use of AJAX.</new>
		<new>Hebrew translation - thanks PozaTive!</new>
		<new>Email Notifications. Subscribe to forum, topic or person.</new>
		<new>Converter APIs now made completely dynamic. You can even add new converters to the Tools screen now from a system or ninjaboard plugin.</new>
		<new>More forum icons, this time selected icons from WooCons.</new>
		<upgrade>bbCode parser now matches urls, using http://daringfireball.net/2010/07/improved_regex_for_matching_urls/ but without allowing javascript, file, jar or data protocols.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Avatars resizing now also crops, while maintaining aspect ratio. Making sure images always have the specified dimensions.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Permalinks now include the post date, not just the tiny icon to the left of it.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>SEF urls are optimized and tweaked. One of the changes is the /forum/ part is gone (but those old urls work so don't worry about any 404s).</upgrade>
		<upgrade>phpBB3 converter upgraded to support shadow topics, avatars and attachments.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>phpBB3 converter is now configured by specifying the path to the installation. Database details are fetched from the forum configuration instead of manually entering them.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Ninjaboard 0.5 converter now supports avatars and attachments. Meaning the migration support to 1.0 is 100% complete!</upgrade>
		<upgrade>bbCode updated to support [list=] for ordered lists, [size] support added, [quote] implementation improved.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Kunena converter upgraded to support avatars, shadow topics and attachments.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Major overhaul to Converter API and UI.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>List styling is more minimal than before.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Menu XML updated to work with 1.6</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Upgraded from GPLv2 to GPLv3</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Database schema upgrades no longer runs during install, but on first load post install. This prevents script timeouts while upgrading your forums.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Forums in the admin now sort by custom ordering by default to avoid confusion.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>The forums on the frontend now order by custom ordering by default, instead of by id.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>ACL queries are now much more conditional. Resulting in 10x faster loadtimes.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Better dates display, instead of "2 months" ago you get "12 aug".</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Nooku Framework updated to rev2646</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Updated French translation - thanks Xavier!</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Updated Dutch translation - thanks John Bartels!</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Better button alignments on frontend forms.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>mod_breadcrumbs is now autorendered when needed, ensuring that the forum navigation is always available.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Sample content are now automatically imported on fresh installs. Making Ninjaboard work more out of the box.</upgrade>
		<bugfix>Increased converter ajax timeout to 400ms to allow /really/ big imports.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Multiple duplicate posts were made if the user clicked multiple times on the Submit button.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Post links always showed the first page in the topic. It now correctly opens the right page with the post. Same is true for redirects and email notification links.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>SEO Setting -> Add Suffix to URL broke file attachment links.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed fatal error after Ninjaboard 0.5 migrations due to empty ninjaboard_user_group_maps table.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>phpBB3 bbCode not properly converted - thanks for the patch Yireo!</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Resolved conflict with Fabrik in relations to SEF.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Rank icons set to a fixed height of 16px in some places.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Some buttons, like Delete topic, had a style attribute with display:inline breaking some layouts.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Topics and Posts columns in the forum admin were swapped.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed MAX_JOIN_SIZE issue due to large joins in the acl queries.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Problem with clicking checkboxes in lists fixed.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed forums ordering issue where Forums with an ID like 13 came before 8.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Show username setting in configuration wasn't working</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Image helper for resizing avatars now fully supports the FTP Layer.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Default avatar changed when gravatar got turned on.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Gravatars didn't work with allow_url_fopen=off, changed to cURL helper instead of JFile::read.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>console.log debug call caused the delete button to not work in other browsers than Chrome, Safari and Firefox.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Orphan topics incorrectly showed up in Latest Topics lists.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Backend user edit view now correctly reveal default assigned usergroups, not just manual overrides.</bugfix>
		<log>The "Forums title for subforums" option deprecated as no one ever use it.</log>
	</state>

	<version>1.0.0RC5</version>
	<date>September 17th 2010</date>
	<state>Minor Release
		<bugfix>Ajax requests, like post deletion, seized functioning when SEF + URL suffix were turned on.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Avatars failed to render when SEF with URL suffix were enabled on the site.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Default avatars sometimes didn't render if Gravatar were enabled.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Warp5.5 changed how module chrome works, and thus Chameleon failed to take on Warp5.5 template styling.</bugfix>
	</state>

	<version>1.0.0RC4</version>
	<date>September 16th 2010</date>
	<state>Major Release
		<new>Basic user profile editing frontend. Set avatar and forum signature.</new>
		<new>Avatars now got cached thumbnails. Supports both GD2 and ImageMagick</new>
		<new>Gravatar support added.</new>
		<upgrade>RTL support complete.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Basic forms validation added to topics creation, replying and editing.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Confirmation dialog when deleting topics and posts to prevent accidental deletions.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Removed br tags from forum titles. Using span{display:block} instead.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Forum descriptions are no longer cut off in forums view.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Posts count displayed, not just ranks and stars.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Forum and Topic toolbar now both top and bottom.</upgrade>
		<bugfix>Color and font size dropdowns in posts editor were visible on page load.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>No longer possible to create topics and posts without a subject and text.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed issue with Artisteer templates that caused the delete topic button to fail.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed FireFox error while editing post.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed duplicate subject titles in topic view.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed translation errors in core.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Tooltips were broken.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Impossible to delete avatar.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Added missing translation strings from the menu manager.</bugfix>
	</state>

	<version>1.0.0RC3</version>
	<date>September 9th 2010</date>
	<state>Minor Release
		<new>Swedish translation - thanks Kristian Dahlén!</new>
		<bugfix>Check for updates failed when open_basedir were set.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Dutch translation failed to install due to missing tags in manifest.xml</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Ninjaboard usergroups mapper have 0 as the default value, but looks like it's the first most Ninjaboard group visually speaking. Now the default value is exactly what you expect it to be.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>If a forum alias started with an number, it would 404 frontend when SEF turned on.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Forum reordering arrows worked reversed.</bugfix>
	</state>

	<version>1.0.0RC2</version>
	<date>September 7th 2010</date>
	<state>Minor Release
		<bugfix>Error when adding forum fixed.</bugfix>
	</state>

	<version>1.0.0RC1</version>
	<date>September 1st 2010</date>
	<state>Major Release
		<new>Dutch translation and improved localization support in core - thanks John 'cQuencer' Bartels!</new>
		<upgrade>No sort/reorder option in forums.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Improved button markup.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Pagination now consistent.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Forum descriptions are now an h3 tag, instead of css2 generated content (using ::after).</upgrade>
		<bugfix>Rounded Chameleon failed to apply the hover hilite on the top border, while squared worked as expected.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed issue with enable, disable and default toolbar actions.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Avatar upload works properly again.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Several bugfixes made to the Users view. Ranks, Ninjaboard usergroups all display correctly now.</bugfix>
	</state>

	<version>1.0.0Beta6</version>
	<date>August 31st 2010</date>
	<state>Major Release
		<new>French translation - thanks Xavier!</new>
		<new>Greek translation - thanks Kostas M.!</new>
		<new>Refreshed list view UI.</new>
		<bugfix>Items 5-10 disappeared when j! global config -&gt; list lenght = 5.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed issue in Ninjaboard 0.5 converter.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Forum permissions sometimes didn't save correctly.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Topics didn't show more than 6 posts, and no pagination.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Issue when deleting posts and topics solved.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed css double spaces and @import usage that broke in RokGZipper.</bugfix>
	</state>

	<version>1.0.0Beta5 take 6</version>
	<date>August 8th 2010</date>
	<state>Minor Release
		<upgrade credit="Lintzy">English and German translations improved.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Backend list view shows more clearly which rows you got selected.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Forums frontend now have a default icon.</upgrade>
		<bugfix>Kunena converter failed to import the replies count, last post id on topics, and the post dates.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Regression in post preview ajax.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed a rare case where the guest user failed to map correctly.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>If you edited a post, only the attachments for that post were visible after redirect.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed saving error in usegroup maps.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Latest topics feature under Forums view were broken.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Typo in topics model caused a performance issue.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>A regression caused permissions not to apply to the "Latest topics" list.</bugfix>
	</state>

	<version>1.0.0Beta5 take 5</version>
	<date>August 5th 2010</date>
	<state>Minor Release
		<upgrade>German translation updated.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Changed wording of usergroups reminder.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Extension updater in dashboard now displays error messages on failure.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Firefox issue with converters resolved.</upgrade>
		<bugfix>Kunena converter is fixed, and thus re-enabled.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed regression where topics more than 10 but less than 20 wouldn't show until the total were bigger than 20.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed pagination php notices and warnings.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed regression in search plugin.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>AJAX conflict fixed with extensions like Sobi2 and JomSocial.</bugfix>
	</state>

	<version>1.0.0Beta5 take 4</version>
	<date>August 4th 2010</date>
	<state>Minor Release
		<bugfix>Resolved php notices in the admin stats module.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>No longer showing views in menu manager that can't be used yet.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Resolved redirect problem when cancelling creations, replies and editing of posts and topics.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Resolving breadcrumbs problem.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Forums were in the wrong order on forums view.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed uninstall regression.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed PHP notices and warnings frontend and admin.</bugfix>
		
	</state>

	<version>1.0.0Beta5 take 3</version>
	<date>August 2nd 2010</date>
	<state>Minor Release focusing on Attachments
		<upgrade>Added option under Settings allowing you to change wether to view attachments inline, or download them.</upgrade>
		<bugfix>Regression in post controller caused the post_id not being set in uploaded attachments.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Attachments showed while editing a post, listed the obfuscated names instead of the real ones.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Attachments view didn't support the FTP layer.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>The mime type were always text/html, except for PDFs, causing images to be turned into weird characters when viewed directly (not in the img tag)</bugfix>
	</state>

	<version>1.0.0Beta5 take 2</version>
	<date>August 1st 2010</date>
	<state>Minor Release
		<upgrade>Text color set to white instead of semi-transparent on Usergroups labels to improve readability.</upgrade>
		<bugfix>Bug in Mapper prevented FireFox to save the Mappings consistently.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Icon alignment without left margin in topics lists when using light Chameleon.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Topic ajax preview had a regression and didn't actually preview your post.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Forum per forum chameleon settings couldn't be set to inherit the current settings profile.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Regression where guests were unable to see forums on some servers setups.</bugfix>
	</state>

	<version>1.0.0Beta5 take 1</version>
	<date>July 27th 2010</date>
	<state>Major Release
		<new>Views like Forums in the admin now have maintenance mode that runs once per week. They will automatically fix table relations and such when needed.</new>
		<new>Full downgrade support. Ninjaboard 0.5 tables are backed up during install, and will be recovered during uninstall to allow downgrades.</new>
		<new>Users can now be assigned to more than one usergroup at once.</new>
		<new>Possible to adjust spacing between forum boxes</new>
		<new>Custom designed premium topic icons, exclusively for Ninjaboard.</new>
		<new>Person page frontend. Shows the avatar, user rank and the persons latest topics.</new>
		<new>Auto-translator, updates your NB language file with untranslated strings for your convenience. Turn on Language debugging under Global Config to activate it.</new>
		<new>Tools screen upgraded</new>
		<new>Norwegian translation on frontend.</new>
		<upgrade>Ninjaboard Stats Admin Module. Go to the module manager &gt; administrator and publish it to ninjaboard-dashboard-tabs.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Chameleons compatibility with Gantry Framework and Warp5 are improved.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Views like the forums and topics views are now taking advantage of HMVC.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>The forms styling when creating a topic, posting a reply or editing a post are now even sexier and more user friendly.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Usergroups are now easier to setup, as you get a live, human readable paragraph to the right explaining your permissions configurations.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Improved the Sample Content available on the Tools screen.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Added option to not make the forums title in forums view linkable. Instead of just showing a permalink, or making it linkable (which don't work well in all templates)</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Much more localizable, javascript that were previously hardcoded, now uses JText for translatability.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Forums styling is enhanced to take advantage of more CSS3 features, and subtle hilites between rows that change correctly based on mouse hover.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Ninjaboard 1.0 can now install on a 0.5 site, and it'll present you an option to import the 0.5 data into your 1.0 database after upgrade.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Styling of moderation tools frontend upgraded to use Chameleon.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Advanced CSS3 (like gradients) no longer favor WebKit based browsers. Gecko and Presto support added.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Usability of usergroup Mapper is improved. Easier to click and drag, and mouseover highlight the end point.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>phpBB3 converter vastly improved.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Converter speeds are dramatically faster. Things that used to take 3 hours, now take literally 3 minutes.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Major speed improvements, queries no longer recurse!</upgrade>
		<upgrade>bbCode parser upgraded to support more tags, like table tags.</upgrade>
		<bugfix>Super admins didn't have full permissions at all times.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>In some cases the acl didn't apply as expected.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Forums view show the correct username, instead of just "Anonymous"</bugfix>
		<bugfix>SEF issue with posting now fixed.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Uninstalling com_ninja before the ninja system plugin used to break the joomla site.</bugfix>
	</state>

	<version>1.0.0Beta4 take 3</version>
	<date>May 13th 2010</date>
	<state>Converter Release
		<new>phpBB3 converter</new>
		<upgrade>Major upgrades and enhancements to the converters UI.</upgrade>
	</state>

	<version>1.0.0Beta4 take 2</version>
	<date>May 10th 2010</date>
	<state>Quickfix
		<bugfix>No Access - Didn't work on a per forum basis.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fatal error when editing settings</bugfix>
	</state>

	<version>1.0.0Beta4 take 1</version>
	<date>May 9th 2010</date>
	<state>Quickfix
		<bugfix>Chameleon not working on topics.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Linked forum titles have terrible colors.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed a rare case of wsod frontend with a "E_FATAL #3 argument is not an array" error.</bugfix>
	</state>

	<version>1.0.0Beta4</version>
	<date>May 8th 2010</date>
	<state>Major Release
		<new>A hint message is displayed in Usergroups about the "Maps" feature.</new>
		<new>Two module positions now available in the admin dashboard. 'ninjaboard-dashboard-tabs' and 'ninjaboard-dashboard-accordions'.</new>
		<new>Admin stats module, to be used in the dashboard.</new>
		<bugfix>Fixed sortables in Settings view.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed PHP 5.3 call-time pass-by-reference warning in the post controller</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed "New Topic" button that was shown to users who don't have post access</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed behavior.livetitle that were using shorttags</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed IE bug in toolbar.js</bugfix>
		<bugfix>The sample content importer didn't import usergroup permissions correctly, neither did the mappings.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Permissions got mixed up if you logged in as a different user, due to a session issue</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Forum per forum permissions didn't apply properly on frontend.</bugfix>
		<upgrade>Backend usergroups view now display the rules so you can at glance see how the usergroups are setup.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>You're now notified in the usergroups backend if a group don't have permission rules defined (as caused by the fault in the sample content importer).</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Forums titles are now linkable.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Possible to hide the "Forums" title.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Improved german translation - thanks Lintzy!</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Forum per forum permissions got a code refactor, and UI redesign.</upgrade>
	</state>

	<version>1.0.0Beta3</version>
	<date>April 19th 2010</date>
	<state>Major Release
		<new>Remote updater built right into the dashboard, staying up to date is just one click's effort</new>
		<bugfix>Usergroups saving error fixed.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Error when assigning a specific user to a specific usergroup.</bugfix>
		<upgrade>FireFox CSS3 support now on the same level and degree as for WebKit.</upgrade>
	</state>

	<version>1.0.0Beta2</version>
	<date>April 5th 2010</date>
	<state>Major Release
		<upgrade>Settings that isn't active yet, are hidden until stable.</upgrade>
		<new>Latest topics support</new>
		<new>Attachments with acl support.</new>
		<upgrade>All post dates change based on the user locale correctly.</upgrade>
		<new>Complete core SEF support.</new>
		<bugfix>When a user posts, the posts count for that user correctly updates, but only if the post were made.</bugfix>
		<upgrade>Post stats bubble up the tree, meaning that the latest post in a child forum, is also the latest post in the parent forum.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Forums can now override some chameleon settings on a per-forum basis.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Complete permissions control per-forum.</upgrade>
		<new>Integrates with core search.</new>
		<new>We now got full css, js, images and html layouts overridability for Morph themelets.</new>
		<upgrade>Overal stability improved.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Sample content importer now works.</upgrade>
		<bugfix>Disabled forums no longer display frontend.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Frontend forums were unbrowsable if not logged in.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Breadcrumbs now works again.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Odd behavior where forums would be duplicated down the tree on first load, but load correctly on second load.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Sometimes the add/edit forum, and add/edit usergroup screen would produce a fatal error.</bugfix>
	</state>

	<version>1.0.0Beta1</version>
	<date>March 14th 2010</date>
	<state>Major Release
		<new>Sample content, Ninjaboard and Kunena importers in the tools screen.</new>
		<new>The toolbar now got keyboard shortcuts.</new>
		<upgrade>More interactive toolbar, only show buttons when needed.</upgrade>
		<upgrade>Installing 1.0 over an existing 0.5 installation is now 100% safe.</upgrade>
		<bugfix>ACL defaults are now much more out-of-the-box.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Subforums are now behaving more properly when changing parent forums.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Usergroups couldn't save due to a bug in the controller.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Dropped the #__ninjaboard_view_forums table view as it caused errors on 0.5 =&gt; 1.0 migrations.</bugfix>
	</state>

	<version>1.0.0Alpha2</version>
	<date>February 6th 2010</date>
	<state>Minor Release
		<upgrade>New and improved ACL (Permissions) system based on feedback from tester group and the Nooku Framework team.</upgrade>
		<bugfix>Solved issues related to forums that made forums invisible on the backend when disabled.</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Various other bugfixes and small improvements and tweaks to Ninjaboard in overall.</bugfix>
	</state>

	<version>1.0.0Alpha1</version>
	<date>February 1st 2010</date>
	<state>Major Release
		<new>All code from scratch using Nooku Framework</new>
		<new>Auto skinning template engine</new>
		<new>User friendly backend UI, and much much more</new>
	</state>
	
	<version>0.5.4</version>
	<date>01:24 AM Nov 14st 2009</date>
	<state>Maintenance Release
		<!-- Bugfixes -->
		<bugfix>Fixed PHP 5.3 incompatibility issues with the use of ereg(). Replaced with strstr().</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Fixed an issue with ninjaboard_blue style that made the css fail to load on domains with paths.</bugfix>
	</state>
	
	<version>0.5.3</version>
	<date>6:04 AM Aug 21st 2009</date>
	<state>Maintenance Release
		<!-- Bugfixes -->
		<bugfix>Important fix to long, multipage threads</bugfix>
		<!-- Improved Features -->
		<new>Subject can be disabled for replies, and is auto-populated</new>
	</state>

	<version>0.5.2</version>
	<date>6:04 AM Aug 21st 2009</date>
	<state>Minor Feature and Bugfix Release
		<!-- Bugfixes -->
		<bugfix>Minor fixes to BBCode - size and lists</bugfix>
		<!-- Improved Features -->
		<upgrade>Buttons completely reworked to be text with a background image, not pure images. This allows for MUCH easier translation and fixes a few issues people were having with invisible buttons.</upgrade>
	</state>
	
	<version>0.5.1beta</version>
	<date>5:00 PM Aug 9th 2009</date>
	<state>Feature and Bugfix Release
		<!-- Bugfixes -->
		<bugfix>Jpeg added to default avatar file types (not just jpg)</bugfix>
		<bugfix>Signatures now allow BBcode</bugfix>
		<bugfix>posts from unpublished forums no longer appear in latest posts</bugfix>
		<bugfix>rank shows in preview correctly</bugfix>
		<bugfix>special characters no longer break forum names</bugfix>
		<!-- Localization Improvements-->
		<locale>Default install data now translatable</locale>
		<!-- Refactored or cleaned up code. Code that doesn't fix anything or add any features -->
		<log> Some back end screens made fully MVC</log>
		<log>Miscellaneous CSS changes to output for easier readability</log>
		<!-- New Features -->
		<new>BBcode Editor</new>
		<new>Attachments engine. Can define file types and image types for attachments</new>
		<new>BBcode Parser for greater security</new>
		<new>Category appears in breadcrumb</new>
		<!-- User Interface improvements -->
		<ui title="Back-end User Interface">Timezone and time format lists reformatted to be easier to understand</ui>
		<!-- Improved Features -->
		<upgrade>Quotes now show who said it</upgrade>
		<upgrade>code beautifier for [code] tags</upgrade>
	</state>
	
	<version>0.5.0beta</version>
	<date>May 2009</date>
	<state>First Release
		<log>Initial beta version release of Ninjaboard.</log>
	</state>
	
</changelogs>